<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[WOWEN® FemTech – Insights]]></title><description><![CDATA[Expertise in full-stack development, femtech, UX, design, and marketing.]]></description><link>https://www.wowen.tech/insights</link><image><url>https://www.wowen.tech/assets/img/apple-touch-icon.png</url><title>WOWEN® FemTech – Insights</title><link>https://www.wowen.tech/insights</link></image><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 23:30:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.wowen.tech/insights/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[This is a test article 3]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am testing this RSS feed. Test, test, test 3. […]
]]></description><link>https://www.wowen.tech/insights/test2/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wowen.tech/insights/test2/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 18:28:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[This is a test article 2]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am testing this RSS feed. Test, test, test 2. […]
]]></description><link>https://www.wowen.tech/insights/test2/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wowen.tech/insights/test2/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 19:28:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[This is a test article]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am testing this RSS feed. Test, test, test. […]
]]></description><link>https://www.wowen.tech/insights/test/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wowen.tech/insights/test/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 20:28:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[World's First Fertility Awareness AI: Democratizing Health Wisdom for Every Woman]]></title><description><![CDATA[Women often find themselves funneling substantial amounts of money into personal healthcare, navigating the costly waters of courses or private sessions with Fertility Awareness Health Care Educators. While it's understood that these professionals deserve their due, this financial barrier starkly contrasts with the ideal of universal bodily autonomy. After all, without deep knowledge of one's own body, how can anyone make truly informed decisions? The […]
]]></description><link>https://www.wowen.tech/insights/worlds-first-fertility-awareness-ai/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wowen.tech/insights/worlds-first-fertility-awareness-ai/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:14:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Women Are Empowered, Men Have Power]]></title><description><![CDATA[In recent years, "empowerment" has become a trendy catchphrase, plastered across social media, marketing campaigns, and corporate initiatives. It's a term that holds an air of inspiration and aspiration, promising a world where women break free from the shackles of patriarchy and assert their agency. But does this buzzword hold any substantial meaning, or is it merely a pretty package and a mirage in the […]
]]></description><link>https://www.wowen.tech/insights/women-are-empowered-men-have-power/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wowen.tech/insights/women-are-empowered-men-have-power/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 12:14:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Smart Tech – That Makes You Stupid?]]></title><description><![CDATA[As my reliance on technology grows, I can't help but notice a diminishing connection between my own body and the organic world that surrounds me. It's ironic that while I can compose intricate scripts, deciphering the complexities of my own physical being proves to be an elusive endeavor. Moreover, the human body can be seen as an intricately sophisticated biological code, making this contrast all the more intriguing […]
]]></description><link>https://www.wowen.tech/insights/smart-tech-that-makes-you-stupid/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wowen.tech/insights/smart-tech-that-makes-you-stupid/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 09:56:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FemTech: A Minefield of Promising Ideas, And Crap?]]></title><description><![CDATA[While FemTech comes with many promising ideas, there are also concerns that some of the products and services offered are more about marketing hype than actual health benefits. The packaging of these products is often very attractive, and they are marketed with buzzwords like "empowerment" and "self-care." However, the reality is that some of these products are more about making money than they are about improving your health. […]
]]></description><link>https://www.wowen.tech/insights/femtech-a-minefield-of-promising-ideas-and-crap/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wowen.tech/insights/femtech-a-minefield-of-promising-ideas-and-crap/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 14:53:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hot Flashes, Cool Tech: How FemTech is Bringing Relief to Menopause]]></title><description><![CDATA[FemTech is revolutionizing menopause management with innovative solutions like apps and wearables. This article delves into how technology is bringing relief to women during this natural aging process. Despite being a significant stage in every woman's life, it's surprising that […]
]]></description><link>https://www.wowen.tech/insights/hot-flashes-cool-tech-how-femtech-is-bringing-relief-to-menopause/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wowen.tech/insights/hot-flashes-cool-tech-how-femtech-is-bringing-relief-to-menopause/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 13:59:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FemTech And Data Security: Is Your Data Safe?]]></title><description><![CDATA[From fertility trackers to breast pumps, these innovative products and services are empowering women around the world. However, with the rise of FemTech also comes the need to protect your personal data. Health tracking apps can collect unimaginable amounts of data about you and this can include your location, your […]
]]></description><link>https://www.wowen.tech/insights/femtech-and-data-security/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wowen.tech/insights/femtech-and-data-security/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 12:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Disconnected in a Connected World: The Rising Epidemic of Isolation in the Digital Age]]></title><description><![CDATA[In today's world, we are more connected to everything than ever before. We can instantly communicate with anyone, anywhere in the world, and access an almost infinite amount of information at our fingertips in a split of seconds. At the same time, we are the loneliest and most isolated humans in history. Yet, despite the unprecedented level of […]
]]></description><link>https://www.wowen.tech/insights/disconnected-in-a-connected-world/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wowen.tech/insights/disconnected-in-a-connected-world/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:51:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Everything and Everyone is Binary: From Micro to Macro]]></title><description><![CDATA[While non-binary identities have gained popularity, recognition and acceptance, the fundamental role of binary processes in the natural world remains unchanged. From the microcosm of our cells to the vastness of the universe, everything and everyone is binary; in fact, you wouldn't even be alive if you weren't binary, down to the cellular level – and many more essential functions rely on binary systems. So even as we embrace and […]
]]></description><link>https://www.wowen.tech/insights/everything-is-binary/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wowen.tech/insights/everything-is-binary/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 12:30:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Designing with Harmony: How "The Universal One" Principles Can Enhance Your Designs]]></title><description><![CDATA[In the beginning, there was rhythm. "The Universal One" is a seminal work by Walter Russell, a scientist, artist, and philosopher who proposed a unified theory of everything that encompasses all aspects of the universe, from atoms to galaxies. While the book covers a wide range of topics, including cosmology, spirituality, and metaphysics, there are some valuable principles that can be applied to design work. In this article, we'll explore […]
]]></description><link>https://www.wowen.tech/insights/designing-with-harmony-how-the-universal-one-principles-can-enhance-your-design-process/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wowen.tech/insights/designing-with-harmony-how-the-universal-one-principles-can-enhance-your-design-process/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 12:30:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chaos Marketing: How to Implement Chaos Magick in Marketing Strategies]]></title><description><![CDATA[Over 30 000 new leads in 5 days and a 140 % increase in user acquisition. My colleague looked at me with gazing eyes and asked me what kind of black magic I used. Little did he know, I am in fact using magic in my work – being an avid reader of esoteric knowledge, ancient occult scripts, and alchemy; I bring this into my profession and have seen the results of it, again and again, and again. Marketers can create a powerful brand identity that resonates with their target audience and drives growth by focusing on […]
]]></description><link>https://www.wowen.tech/insights/chaos-marketing/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wowen.tech/insights/chaos-marketing/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 12:30:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Harnessing the Power of Menstruation: With Cycle-Sync Strategies]]></title><description><![CDATA[Menstrual cycles are a natural and normal part of life for women, yet often overlooked regarding productivity and peak performance. Harnessing the power of our menstrual cycle to maximize productivity is a concept that is still relatively new and unknown and definitely not something you think about in workplaces or in terms of work culture. However, understanding […]
]]></description><link>https://www.wowen.tech/insights/harnessing-the-power-of-menstruation-maximize-productivity-with-cycle-sync-strategies/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wowen.tech/insights/harnessing-the-power-of-menstruation-maximize-productivity-with-cycle-sync-strategies/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 12:30:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[We Should Embrace Laziness More – Or At Least Give It A Bit More Slack]]></title><description><![CDATA[First of all, let’s address the elephant in the room. Yes, we’ve all heard the old adage, “Idle hands are the devil’s workshop”, but I'm here to tell you that this is a load of hocus-pocus. The truth is, sometimes your brain needs a break from the chaos of everyday life. And when it does, there’s nothing more helpful than a little laziness. Think of it this way – your brain is like a racehorse. If you push it too hard, it’ll get exhausted, stumble, and fall flat on its face. But if you let it […]
]]></description><link>https://www.wowen.tech/insights/we-should-embrace-laziness-more-or-at-least-give-it-a-bit-more-slack/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wowen.tech/insights/we-should-embrace-laziness-more-or-at-least-give-it-a-bit-more-slack/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 12:30:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>